[{
  "source": "https://travelswithelle.com/other/multiple-choice-trivia-questions/",
  "question": "How many Infinity Stones are there?",
  "answers": ["6", "3", "5", "10"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the only food that cannot go bad?",
  "answers": ["Honey", "Dark chocolate", "Peanut butter", "Canned tuna"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Which was René Magritte’s first surrealist painting?",
  "answers": ["The Lost Jockey", "Not to Be Reproduced", "Personal Values", "The Lovers"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "What 90s boy band member bought Myspace in 2011?",
  "answers": ["Justin Timberlake", "Nick Lachey", "Shawn Stockman", "AJ McLean"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "What is the most visited tourist attraction in the world?",
  "answers": ["Eiffel Tower", "Statue of Liberty", "Great Wall of China", "Colosseum"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What’s the name of Hagrid’s pet spider?",
  "answers": ["Aragog", "Nigini", "Crookshanks", "Mosag"]
}, {
  "question": "What’s the heaviest organ in the human body?",
  "answers": ["Liver", "Brain", "Skin", "Heart"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Who made the third most 3-pointers in the Playoffs in NBA history?",
  "answers": ["Lebron James", "Kevin Durant", "JJ Reddick", "Kyle Korver"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "Which of these EU countries uses the euro as its currency?",
  "answers": ["Spain", "Poland", "Denmark", "Sweden"]
}, {
  "question": "Which US city is the sunniest major city and sees more than 320 sunny days each year?",
  "answers": ["Phoenix", "Miami", "San Francisco", "Austin"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What type of food holds the world record for being the most stolen around the globe?",
  "answers": ["Cheese", "Wagyu beef", "Coffee", "Chocolate"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "What element does the chemical symbol Au stand for?",
  "answers": ["Gold", "Silver", "Magnesium", "Salt"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the highest-grossing Broadway show of all time?",
  "answers": ["The Lion King", "Wicked", "Kinky Boots", "Hamilton"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "On average, how many seeds are located on the outside of a strawberry?",
  "answers": ["200", "100", "400", "500"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "Which fast food restaurant has the largest number of retail locations in the world?",
  "answers": ["Subway", "Jack In The Box", "Chipotle", "McDonald’s"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Where is recognized as the location of the hottest temperature ever recorded on Earth?",
  "answers": ["Death Valley, California", "Mitribah, Kuwait", "Yuma, Arizona", "Key West, Florida"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the oldest soft drink in the United States?",
  "answers": ["Dr. Pepper", "Coca Cola", "Pepsi", "Canada Dry Ginger Ale"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What river passes through New Orleans, Louisiana?",
  "answers": ["Mississippi River", "Orleans River", "Atchafalaya River", "Colorado River"]
}, {
  "question": "In what country do more than half of people believe in elves?",
  "answers": ["Iceland", "Norway", "Russia", "Holland"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the name of the coffee shop in the sitcom Friends?",
  "answers": ["Central Perk", "Java Park", "Central Park Coffee", "Central Park Roastery"]
}, {
  "question": "Which pop star burnt down her home gym with candles?",
  "answers": ["Britney Spears", "Kim Kardashian", "Lady Gaga", "Zendaya"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the highest-grossing video game franchise to date?",
  "answers": ["Pokemon", "Mario", "Call of Duty", "Street Fighter"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "“Cirque du Soleil” started in what country?",
  "answers": ["Canada", "France", "USA", "Russia"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Which country’s national animal is a unicorn?",
  "answers": ["Scotland", "Denmark", "New Zealand", "France"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "Which Avenger other than Captain America was able to pick up Thor’s Mjolnir in the Marvel movies?",
  "answers": ["Vision", "Wanda", "Spiderman", "Doctor Strange"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the main ingredient in a falafel?",
  "answers": ["Chickpea", "Lentil", "Broccoli", "Split pea"]
}, {
  "question": "What color dresses do Chinese women traditionally wear on their wedding day?",
  "answers": ["Red", "Blue", "Gold", "White"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "What is yellowtail fish called in Japanese?",
  "answers": ["Hamachi", "Ahi", "Ikura", "Maguro"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What sport has been played on the moon?",
  "answers": ["Golf", "Frisbee", "Soccer", "Bocce ball"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the highest-grossing holiday movie of all time?",
  "answers": ["Home Alone", "Elf", "Die Hard", "It’s A Wonderful Life"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "What was the first cash crop in America?",
  "answers": ["Tobacco", "Corn", "Sugar Cane", "Grapes"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "Mycology is the scientific study of what?",
  "answers": ["Fungi", "Cancer cells", "Flowers", "Blood"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What animal is the closest living relative of a human?",
  "answers": ["Bonobos", "Gorillas", "Monkeys", "Chimpanzees"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What does the meaning of the word “zodiac” in Ancient Greek?",
  "answers": ["Circle of animals", "Circle of personalities", "Circle of stars", "Circle of futures"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "Aries, Sagittarius, and Leo are three zodiac signs of which element?",
  "answers": ["Fire", "Air", "Water", "Earth"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "The first vaccine was for which disease?",
  "answers": ["Smallpox", "Chickenpox", "Polio", "Measles"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Which Beatle made Elton John the godfather of his son?",
  "answers": ["John Lennon", "Paul McCartney", "Ringo Starr", "George Harrison"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "What lobster organ is made into a delicacy known as “tomalley”?",
  "answers": ["Liver", "Claw", "Tail", "Antennae"],
  "value": 4
}, {
  "question": "The villains in the 2007 version of the movie “Transformers” are known as what?",
  "answers": ["Decepticons", "Storm Troopers", "Death Eaters", "Sentinels"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Which cereal grain is the most commonly used in beer?",
  "answers": ["Barley", "Wheat", "Hops", "Rice"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "“Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull” is based on whose story idea?",
  "answers": ["George Lucas", "Michael Bay", "Ernest Hemingway", "Tim Burton"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What country are the Galapagos Islands located in?",
  "answers": ["Ecuador", "Belize", "Brazil", "Colombia"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "Which sea creature has three hearts?",
  "answers": ["Octopus", "Shark", "Jellyfish", "Stingray"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Pupusas are from what country?",
  "answers": ["El Salvador", "Mexico", "Brazil", "Poland"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the name of the talkative parrot in “Aladdin”?",
  "answers": ["Iago", "Pascal", "Meeko", "Abu"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "On “Friends”, what is Ross’ occupation?",
  "answers": ["Paleontologist", "Meteorologist", "News Anchor", "Teacher"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "What is Rick’s last name in “Rick and Morty”?",
  "answers": ["Sanchez", "Smith", "Guetterman", "Noopers"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "Where did the croissant originate?",
  "answers": ["Austria", "France", "Turkey", "Tokyo"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "In what U.S. state does “Breaking Bad” take place?",
  "answers": ["New Mexico", "Utah", "Missouri", "Texas"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What country is Shakira from?",
  "answers": ["Colombia", "Mexico", "Puerto Rico", "Paraguay"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "Mount Olympus is the highest mountain in what country?",
  "answers": ["Greece", "Italy", "Spain", "Portugal"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "Which country ranks first in cereal consumption per capita?",
  "answers": ["Ireland", "USA", "Italy", "Philippines"],
  "value": 4
}, {
  "question": "From which country do French fries originate?",
  "answers": ["Belgium", "France", "USA", "England"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What sport is referred to as the “sport of kings”?",
  "answers": ["Polo", "Bocce Ball", "Cricket", "Rugby"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Who was the first Disney Princess?",
  "answers": ["Snow White", "Cinderella", "Aurora", "Jasmine"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "What year was In-N-Out Burger founded?",
  "answers": ["1948", "1968", "1975", "1985"],
  "value": 4
}, {
  "question": "How many islands are in Hawaii?",
  "answers": ["137", "4", "7", "48"],
  "value": 4
}, {
  "question": "What is the national alcoholic beverage of America?",
  "answers": ["Bourbon", "Rye", "Whiskey", "Cognac"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "What is Bruno Mars’ real name?",
  "answers": ["Peter Gene Hernandez", "Michael Nguyen-Stevenson", "Ray Aguirre", "Bruno Madrigal"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "What was the very first Pixar movie?",
  "answers": ["Toy Story", "Wall-E", "Monsters, Inc.", "A Bug’s Life"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "What was the ancient Goddess of Love?",
  "answers": ["Venus", "Athena", "Helen", "Hera"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What are imitation crab sticks made of?",
  "answers": ["Whitefish", "Cuttlefish", "Tofu", "Calamari"],
  "value": 3
}, {
  "question": "Which ocean is the Bermuda Triangle in?",
  "answers": ["Atlantic Ocean", "Pacific Ocean", "Caribbean Ocean", "Indian Ocean"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Where is Kanye West from?",
  "answers": ["Chicago, Illinois", "Boston, Massachusetts", "Detroit, Michigan", "Los Angeles, California"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the smallest country in the world?",
  "answers": ["The Vatican City", "Luxembourg", "Palau", "San Marino"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What animal species is the only male that gets pregnant?",
  "answers": ["Seahorse", "Dolphin", "Elephant Seal", "Sea Turtle"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "Who was the first woman to ever be inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?",
  "answers": ["Aretha Franklin", "Dolly Parton", "Janis Joplin", "Joni Mitchell"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "What is the hardest natural substance in the world?",
  "answers": ["Diamond", "Granite", "Marble", "Iron"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "Which “Wonders Of The World” is still in existence?",
  "answers": ["Pyramids of Giza", "Temple of Artemis", "Hanging Gardens of Babylon", "Statue of Zeus"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
  "answers": ["Leonardo da Vinci", "Michelangelo", "Vincent van Gogh", "Rembrandt"],
  "value": 1
}, {
  "question": "Which company was the first to reach 1 trillion dollars?",
  "answers": ["Apple", "Microsoft", "Amazon", "Google"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "Which animal has the largest eyes?",
  "answers": ["Giant squid", "Blue whale", "Ostrich", "Elephant"],
  "value": 2
}, {
  "question": "From what country did jazz originate?",
  "answers": ["USA", "France", "Canada", "Germany"],
  "value": 2
}]